Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 119: Unions rebuff Brown on water program, 1960; Publication (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 120: Algeria spurns talks, Meany asks UN move, 1960; Publication (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 121: Unions Marshal vote effort, 1960; Publication (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 122: Labor puts stand on political line, 1960; Publication (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 123: AMA acts to counter labor on care for aged, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 124: AFL-CIO levels big guns on amended labor bill, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 125: Unionism at the crossroads, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 126: Union bias is charge by NAACP, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 127: US labor leaders convene with verbal guns blazing, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 128: Anti-Red groups strive for Khrushchev visit focus, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 129: Puerto Rican labor held betrayed, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 130: Eisenhower offers strong labor bill, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 131: Rival unions paid men $5 an hour for meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 132: ALF-CIO selling self to public, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 133: Meany hints third party, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 134: Labor chiefs plan to rally votes for '60, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 135: NAM assails Murrow over call-girl story, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 136: Unions delay in Hutcheson ethics case, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 137: AFL-CIO asks OAS to isolate dictators, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 138: Union failure on evils seen by Kennedy, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 139: Ex-Ford employees sue Reuther over jobs, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 140: NLRB aid restates finding against Kohler, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 141: AFL-CIO to meet in Puerto Rico, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 142: Labor Party plan draws criticism, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 143: AFL-CIO assails Nixon tax proposal, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 144: AFL-CIO forbids Hoffa alliances, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 145: Meany hits business on labor bill, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 146: Eisenhower jogs labor reforms, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 147: Meany Parley plan faces big hurdles, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 148: Big labor and challenge, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 149: Ives meets unions on job issue, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 150: Organizing scientists a problem to unions, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 151: AFL-CIO battles labor rackets here, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 152: AFL-CIO bars aid to teamsters, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 153: AFL-CIO truce on teamsters ebbs, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 154: Meany describes advance in AFL-CIO efforts for..., 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 155: AFL-CIO checked in South..., 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 156: Labor maps drive, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 157: AFL-CIO Executive Council challenges teamsters union, 1958-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 158: AFL-CIO votes a 2d crackdown, 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 159: AFL-CIO limits labor-law support, 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 160: Spellman hits union gangsters, 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 161: Unionists rap proposal for pay boost holdback, 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 162: AFL-CIO suspends bake union, 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 163: Meany bars compromise, 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 164: AFL-CIO grasps for clean unity, 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 165: Clue waited to AFL-CIO action..., 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 166: Meany charges fund corruption, 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 167: Meany demands housecleaning in employer-run welfare funds, 1957-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 168: Policy Controversy, 1956-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 169: AFL-CIO rocked by foreign, 1956-1959 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 170: State, City labor join racket fight, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 171: Meany backs Dubinsky's fight on unionists with business ties, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 172: Meany aids move to oust unionists in business rules, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 173: Indians acclaim Reuther's visit, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 174: AFL-Cio urges US extend wage floor, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 175: Rackets trials set for 3 unions, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 176: Meany, Reuther split over India, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 177: Unions seek shorter week, rail, dock issues undecided, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 178: Unions map lure to office worker, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 179: AFL-CIO plans to help refugees, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 180: Labor urges free world take more vigorous role in crises, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 181: Union bid fizzles, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 182: Kirkland, aide to Meany, elected to no. 2 spot in AFL-CIO, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 183: Meany sees democrats losing workers' support, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 184: Unionist for Rockefeller, 1956-1970 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 185: Meany sees Democrats losing workers' support, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 186: Unions to build labor college, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 187: Labor convention is torn by choice for Governor, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 188: State labor split on Governorship, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 189: AFL-CIO chiefs to press for 35-hour work week, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 190: Welshing on torch gifts hit by labor leaders, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 191: Strike settled in Grand Haven, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 192: AFL-CIO Parley seeks huge '62 voter turnout, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 193: AFL hits city 'taxation without representation', 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 194: AFL-CIO to seek 35-hour week, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 195: Labor opens attack on new constitution, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 196: AFL-CIO ready to hurl formal blast at con-con, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 197: Unions switch given credit for Ok of tax plan, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 198: County AFL-CIO to spur demands for police raises, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 199: Reuther, Williams due to join in AFL attacks on constitution, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 200: NY pay terms agreed indraft teachers' pact, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 201: AFL-CIO rakes con-con with 14-gun broadside, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 202: Profit-squeeze a myth..., 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 203: 35 hr. week given boost by Meany, 1962-1969 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 204: Meany sees ILO slipping from West, 1961-1962 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 205: Rise, fall of Ests' labor pal, 1961-1962 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 206: Gentleman Jerry victim of expensive tastes, 1961-1962 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 207: Labor attacks NAM on jobs vs profits, 1961-1962 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 208: Automation misses goal - AFL-CIO, 1961-1962 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 209: Unions in South stress soft sell, 1961-1962 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - Item 210: 6,500 stike Studebaker, AFL-CIO split widened, 1961-1962 (Box 421, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Fact Sheet - #8 -- Consumer Protection (Get America back to work) AFL-CIO Economic and Legislative Converence, 1962; Publication (Box 422, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Fact Sheet - #6 -- The Crisis in the schools (Get America back to work) AFL-CIO Economic and Legislative Converence, 1962; Publication (Box 422, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: New approaches in labor education, 1957; Publication (Box 422, Folder 1)
    Author: John E. Cosgrove
  - Item 4: Do higher wages cause higher prices?, 1957; Publication (Box 422, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Injustice on trial, 1957; Publication (Box 422, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: In your 1958 Union Education Program - use these films, 1957; Publication (Box 422, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: AFL-CIO Education News and Views - v.2, no. 12; v.2, no. 1, 1957; Publication (Box 422, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: article - Labor education: today and tomorrow, 1956; Publication (Box 422, Folder 1)
    Author: John D. Connors
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Policies for economic growth, 1959; Publication (Box 422, Folder 2)
    Notes: Testimony presented on behalf of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations to the Joint Economic Committee of Congress, on February 9, 1959. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Economic Policy Committee Report to the AFL-CIO Executive Council on Long-Range program required for sustained and balanced economic growth, 1961; Publication (Box 422, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Economic Trends and Outlook, 1960; Publication (Box 422, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.12
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Songs for labor, 1983; Publication (Box 422, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Years of devastation: the 1980s record: loss of jobs, loss of real earnings, crisis in health care, 1992; Publication (Box 422, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor education: today and tomorrow, 1956; Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: ABC's of trade unionism, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: El sindicato obrero y usted, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: La avanzada del progreso, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Progreso y productividad, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Beneficios para todos, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Libertad para siempre, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Benefits for all, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Del sindicalismo, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: The trade union and you, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Freedom forever labor rejects Communism, Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Developing union education committees, 1956; Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: AFL-CIO Education News and Views - v.1, no. 11-12, 1956; Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Teaching guide for use with "The Shop Steward -- key to a strong union", 1956; Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
    Notes: Re-issued by American Federation of labor and the Congress of Industrial Organizations
  - Item 15: 16 mm films for labor, 1956; Publication (Box 422, Folder 4)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Dept. of Education
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Check list for meeting places, Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Free labor meets Khrushchev, Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Helping to write your nation's laws, Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Four year award winners, Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Curtain going up, Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: How to run a union meeting, 1959; Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: AFL-CIO manual for shop stewards, 1959; Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Your library can serve your union, 1959; Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Teaching guide for use with AFL-CIO parliamentary procedure manual 'How to run a union meeting', publication no. 81, 1959; Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Teaching high school students about labor unions, 1959; Publication (Box 422, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Learning can't stop, Publication (Box 422, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Why have public schools?, 1958; Publication (Box 422, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: New approaches in labor education, 1957; Publication (Box 422, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: How to reach the union member, 1958; Publication (Box 422, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: AFL-CIO Education News and Views, 1957-1958 (Box 422, Folder 6)
    Notes: Reprinted from Dec. 1957 and Feb 1958
  - Item 6: AFL-CIO manual for shop steward, 1959; Publication (Box 422, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Teaching guide for use with "AFL-CIO manual for shop stewards", 1950-1959 (Box 422, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Negro and the labor movement, 1970; Publication (Box 422, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Wipe out discrimination., 1960; Publication (Box 422, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Nine steps to a strong and active union, 1960; Publication (Box 422, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Our finest weapon, education, 1960; Publication (Box 422, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A National Conference on Labor Educators on challenges to labor education in the 60's, 1961; Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
    Notes: Sponsored by the National Institute of Labor Education. Conference folder.
  - Item 2: Helping to write your nation's laws, 1961; Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Congressional Record, Proceedings and debates of the 83d Congress, First Session, 1953; Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Labor and antitrust, Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
    Author: Arthur J. Goldberg
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from IUD Digest. 2 copies
  - Item 5: Correspondence - 'Fifty years ago, the AFL Convention under the presidency of Samuel Gompers requested the churches of America', 1960; Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Correspondence - 'We are happy to make available to participants in the national high school debate program this material explaining the policies and work of American trade unions in support of education', Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Correspondence - 'We are sending you the enclosed materials in response to your recent request for information on the application of the antitrust laws to unions', Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: An analysis of antitrust laws and union activity, 1955; Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
    Author: Andrew J. Biemiller
  - Item 9: Facts vs. propaganda; the truth about "Right to Work" laws, 1958; Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Power - for what?, 1958; Publication (Box 422, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Guide to Executive order 10988, 1962; Publication (Box 422, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: 800 films for use in labor education, arranged by subject headings used in labor education, 1963; Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Labor News Conference - Mutual Broadcasting System - Program 27, Series 4, 1964; Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Outline for Report and Discussion of Selected Long-Term Non-Residential labor Education Programs, 1963; Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: New Films added to the AFL-CIO Film Library since January 1963, Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Correspondence - 'Thank you for your letter asking for information about the AFL-CIO merit scholarship program', 1964; Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Exclusive recognition and collective bargaining coverage under executive order 10988: a statistical report, 1965; Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: How to apply - AFL-CIO College Merit Scholarships, Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Report of the Committee on Education to the AFL-CIO, Sixth Convention, 1965; Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Supplement to AFL-CIO's film catalogue 'films for labor', 1963; Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Films on Civil Rights, 1964; Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: The case against Sidney P. Marland, Jr., 1970; Publication (Box 422, Folder 10)
    Author: AFL- CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Dept. of Education
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: AFL-CIO song book, 1957; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Leadership training manual: AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Guide to local union trials, Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
    Author: UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America)
  - Item 4: Aids in the workplace: a steward's manual, Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Why labor supports ERA, Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Simple justice: quality education for all children, Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Helping to write your nation's laws, 1966; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: X-raying colleges, Junior colleges & Technical Institutes, 1966; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Resolution S35 and 138, 1967; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Focus on bargaining: 25 years of progress, Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
    Author: George Ruben
  - Item 11: Public productivity tied to bargaining, 1976; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
    Author: Rudy Oswald
  - Item 12: bound v.of the following - Statement by on the National economy; on New York Towboat strike; on the Civil Rights bill; on Joint declaration; on South Africa; on Youth programs; on National Council on the arts; on Multi-Company ownership of pipe l, 1964; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Executive Council.
  - Item 13: bound v.of the following (goes with above entry) - Waging war against poverty, 1964; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Report - Summary of Statement on the Shorter workweek and the constructive use of free time, Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
    Author: Community Services Committee
  - Item 15: Statement by -- Accelerated public works; Panama; Automation Commission; Mortgage investment trust; Report on cases filed under article XXI; Repeal of Section 14 (b) of the Taft-Hartley Act; Home rule for the Distrivt of Columbia; National Beautif, 1964; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Statement by -- Unemployment Compensation; Report of cases filed under Article XXI; Fair Labor Standards Act Amendments; Background paper on Minimum wage; Federal and postal employee benefits; Viet Nam; The Wage guideline; The National Economy; R, 1966; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Statement by -- Minimum wage and unemployment compensation bills; Collective bargaining with Western Electric; Fair Labor Standards Act; Unemployment Compensation Bill; Civil Rights Act of 1966; Interest rates; The National Economy; Background pa, Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: A report to the Executive Council - Summary of activities in the anti-poverty program, 1966; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Statement by -- Support of OCAW Collective Bargaining objectives; The 90th Congress; Strike at Union Carbide; Social Security and Welfare; Background statement on Social Security and Welfare; National Health Insurance; Inflated medical costs; Une, 1967; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Statement by. -- The growing menace of industrial bond financing; Savings bond campaign; Education and the Federal Govt.; Savings bond campaign; Urban affairs; Air and water pollution; Viet Nam; Consumer legislation; Mounting threat to peace in, 1967; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Statement by -- The war on poverty; Overseas aid; Federal govt. employees; Situs picketing; L.S. Buckmaster; Report on cases filed under Article XXI; The Universal Military Training and Service Act; The National economy; Background statement on, 1967; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Statement by -- The application of Article XXI to collective bargaining relationships with govt. agencies; Support of the American Federation of Teachers; Boycott of Boren Clay Products; Support for the UAW Strike; Support of Strike in the Non-Ferro, 1967; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Statement by -- Harry C. Bates; Runawy plants; Runaway plants to mexican Border Area; American Farm Bureau Federation; Support for strikers in Non-Ferrous Metals Industry; Appropriations for domestic programs; Minimum wage; Child health; Medicaid, 1968; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Statement by -- 50th Anniversary of ILO; Education; The victims of man-made disasters; Donable food and food stamps; Community Services; The Hearst Strike; Report to the AFL-CIO Executive Council on the West Coast Newspaper Strikes; The Copper Str, 1968; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Statement by -- Agency-Union problems; Budget slashing; Consumer credit legislation; Medical costs; The United Auto Workers; The Struggle for Freedom Behind the Iron Curtain; U.S. -Mexican border problems; Giumarra Strike; Growing war danger in t, 1968; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Statement by -- Kayser-Roth Hosiery company strike; Boycott of California grapes; Support of United Federation of Teachers; Los Angeles Herald-Examiner Strike; Confirmation of justice fortas; Soviet occupation of Czechoslovakia; Meeting (Sept. 16, 1968; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Background statement on Uniform Consumer Credit Code, 1968; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Statement by -- Support for the United Farm Workers Strike; Hill-Burton; Support for Local 2, American Federation of Teachers; Day Car Centers; Support for Oil Workers Strike; Economy furniture, Austin, Texas; Formation of AFL-CIO Labor Studies Cen, 1968-1969 (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: Statement by -- Financing Campaign costs; Reapportionment; Dangerous turn in the Middle East; U.S.-Mexican problems; Occupational Safety and Health Legislation; Minimum wage; Economic progress of minorities; Toward eliminating poverty; Background, 1969; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Statement by -- Deter aggression and preserve peace; AFL-CIO and CVT; Stop piracy in the air; Consumer legislation; Strengthen the US Foreign Assistance program; Ralph Helstein; Coordinated Bargaining with General Electric and Westinghouse; Report, 1969; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Statement by -- Housing; Wiretapping and eavesdropping; Election of the President; Federal employees; Report of the Human Resources Development Institute to the., 1969; Publication (Box 423, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 423, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A Report on National Training Policy, 1993; Publication (Box 423, Folder 2)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Ad Hoc Committee on Training
    Notes: May, 1993. 2 copies.
  - Item 2: Six ethical practices codes adopted by the AFL-CIO, 1957; Publication (Box 423, Folder 2)